<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>bioelectronic interfaces on Ran Zhuoheng (Steven)</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/bioelectronic-interfaces/</link>
        <description>Recent content in bioelectronic interfaces on Ran Zhuoheng (Steven)</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/bioelectronic-interfaces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>My paper has been presented at the 2022 IEEE ICSAI Conference 🎉</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/my-paper-has-been-presented-at-the-2022-ieee-icsai-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/my-paper-has-been-presented-at-the-2022-ieee-icsai-conference/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/my-paper-has-been-presented-at-the-2022-ieee-icsai-conference/IEEE.jpg" alt="Featured image of post My paper has been presented at the 2022 IEEE ICSAI Conference 🎉" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank those who have contributed to this work. This is one of the most advanced issues I have discussed until now, in fact many researchers are actively working on visually impaired treatment, but it is still a long way to go before it can be put into use due to the factor like bioadaptability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Title: Hardware Strategies in Medical Systems for Visually Impaired Treatment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract: Millions of blindness and visual impairment cases are caused by damage to the loss of photoreceptor function. Existing experiments and research have shown that electrical stimulation mechanisms can be established through different medical hardware strategies to help visually impaired patients partially recover their vision. Firstly, this paper analyzes the physiological principles to introduce the role of hardware systems in advanced visually impaired treatment schemes. Then, based on worldwide research advances in medical systems for visually impaired treatment, the latest hardware strategies and engineering issues of several representative systems are evaluated and compared in detail. Finally, the development prospect of medical hardware in the medical system is summarized on this basis for more efficient progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information and documents: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/10005387&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
