<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>OneNET Cloud Platform on Ran Zhuoheng</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/onenet-cloud-platform/</link>
        <description>Recent content in OneNET Cloud Platform on Ran Zhuoheng</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/onenet-cloud-platform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Intelligent environment assistant based on uC/OS-iii operating system and OneNET cloud platform</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-environment-assistant-based-on-uc/os-iii-operating-system-and-onenet-cloud-platform/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-environment-assistant-based-on-uc/os-iii-operating-system-and-onenet-cloud-platform/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-environment-assistant-based-on-uc/os-iii-operating-system-and-onenet-cloud-platform/IEEE.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Intelligent environment assistant based on uC/OS-iii operating system and OneNET cloud platform" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;My paper &amp;ldquo;Intelligent environment assistant based on uC/OS-iii operating system and OneNET cloud platform&amp;rdquo; has already been presented at Internet of Things Technologies 🎉.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract: In recent years, with the popularity of smart home products in many households, system intelligence and data visualization have become the trend of such devices. This paper uses the STM32F103 microprocessor development platform to design a smart environment assistant based on the uC/OS-iii operating system and China Mobile&amp;rsquo;s OneNET IoT cloud platform. uC/OS series operating system not only has a lightweight kernel, but also has excellent stability. The OneNET IoT cloud platform provides real-time data collection, location awareness and other services. The system collects and displays environmental parameters such as smoke, PM2.5, temperature and humidity on an LCD screen, and also adds the ability to obtain hazard warning counts and travel advice indices. The GSM/GPRS communication module transmits monitoring data and warning and advice information to the OneNET IoT cloud platform via the MQTT transmission protocol. The user can access the information via PC or mobile app, which greatly improves the time and space limitations of traditional environmental monitoring equipment. The system also uses event flag groups to synchronise different tasks and optimises task priority settings, allowing people to focus on key parameters while achieving low power consumption and saving resources in the cloud. The system is not only suitable for monitoring and alarming hazardous gases in indoor environments, but can also be placed on balconies as an assistant for daily travel advice, which is practical and economical. (translated by software)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China National Knowledge Infrastructure (CNKI) is Now &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.cnki.net/KCMS/detail/detail.aspx?dbcode=CJFD&amp;amp;dbname=CJFDLAST2022&amp;amp;filename=WLWJ202201022&amp;amp;uniplatform=OVERSEA&amp;amp;v=inTBg3hcrz39yagfF4aTW5hOxRPqBPJa-eFL0aC6zQNi26yMT6tybfvkINaJsZSs&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dissertation (Bachelor)</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/dissertation-bachelor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/dissertation-bachelor/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/dissertation-bachelor/University.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Dissertation (Bachelor)" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been working on designing a practical and dedicated system in my undergraduate degree using hardware, IoT and AI, and now it is being implemented and is available in the links on this page. Although it still has limitations, I have used almost most of the tools and experience I learnt at university. I have also found many ideas in practice that were once too ideal, so it was a good try for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this work, I would like to express my gratitude to my undergraduate dissertation supervisor &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://sky.tiangong.edu.cn/2019/0319/c5270a39764/page.htm&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Prof. Huiquan Wang&lt;/a&gt;, who is the Associate Dean of the Faculty of Life Sciences in Tiangong University and guided me on how to make a good design. Eventually, this work was awarded the &amp;ldquo;Outstanding Final Project of Tiangong University&amp;rdquo; because of its rich content (140 pages with 0.8% similarity rate) and technical combinations. My earliest journal was accepted when I was in my second year of undergraduate university. I am doing more and gaining experience to target for potential future research positions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information and documents: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://ranzhuoheng.notion.site/3ca51cd62bb3450aa43c9270b31aef8f?v=b8f436792e90430a95b218d95269d941&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
