<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>LTE network on Ran Zhuoheng</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/lte-network/</link>
        <description>Recent content in LTE network on Ran Zhuoheng</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/lte-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Intelligent agricultural system based on Internet of Things and Cat.1 module</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-agricultural-system-based-on-internet-of-things-and-cat.1-module/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-agricultural-system-based-on-internet-of-things-and-cat.1-module/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/intelligent-agricultural-system-based-on-internet-of-things-and-cat.1-module/IEEE.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Intelligent agricultural system based on Internet of Things and Cat.1 module" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;My paper &amp;ldquo;Intelligent agricultural system based on Internet of Things and Cat.1 module&amp;rdquo; has already been presented at Electronic Design Engineering 🎉.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract: The traditional greenhouse environmental monitoring equipment is not only poor in controllability,but also difficult to ensure the real-time feedback information and visual data. For example,in some parts of southern China,the planting areas of crops are mostly located in remote mountains,hills and valleys and other areas with poor network signal,making a large number of intelligent devices of the Internet of Things unable to play their due advantages and bring actual benefits to farmers. In this paper,an Intelligent agriculture system of the Internet of Things is designed based on Cat.1 module and the cloud platform of the Internet of Things. After testing,the system can not only realize the real-time visualization function of environmental parameter data,but also intelligently adjust and control the work of agricultural facilities such as floodlights and exhaust fans. It can not only save manpower and material resources,but also reduce power consumption. After large-scale deployment,the system can also improve the production quality of crops in the greenhouses,bringing inestimable economic and environmental value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China National Knowledge Infrastructure (CNKI) is Now &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.cnki.net/KCMS/detail/detail.aspx?dbcode=CJFD&amp;amp;dbname=CJFDLAST2022&amp;amp;filename=GWDZ202217018&amp;amp;uniplatform=OVERSEA&amp;amp;v=4oAjxSKVoZ3dAIbRGSvIkH_aY3PFjYIQGrmp6vGWyS2_LPnuJWTUKaZSE1DEc8x5&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
