<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>B60L53/122 on Ran Zhuoheng</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/b60l53/122/</link>
        <description>Recent content in B60L53/122 on Ran Zhuoheng</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/tags/b60l53/122/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Patent Number: CN202210525770.2</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/patent-number-cn202210525770.2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/patent-number-cn202210525770.2/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/patent-number-cn202210525770.2/IEEE.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Patent Number: CN202210525770.2" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work is partly funded under College Students&amp;rsquo; Innovative Entrepreneurial Training Plan Program (202010058055) from Tiangong University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patent Name: A two-way wireless charging system for UAV sets and its path planning design (translated by software)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract: The present invention discloses a two-way wireless charging system for an unmanned aircraft group and its path planning design, in which the structure of the said two-way wireless charging system for an unmanned aircraft group includes a wireless charging base station, two unmanned aircraft and a sensor. The wireless charging base station is equipped with a transmitting coil; the UAV is equipped with a coupling coil; and the sensor is equipped with a receiving coil. When the UAV is located above the sensor or on the wireless charging base station, the corresponding coils are electromagnetically coupled and the UAV charges the sensor or the wireless charging base station charges the UAV. The said path planning design includes constructing a mathematical model of the UAV path, constructing a node selection strategy according to the priority calculation function; generating the initial solution of the model; optimizing the initial solution by means of constraints; and iterating the solution by substituting real-time data to obtain the optimal route. The invention has the advantages of extending the life of the sensor network, saving human and material resources, and is able to operate automatically in some harsh environments or locations that are difficult to reach by humans, which has a wider range of applications. (translated by software)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China Invention Patents is Now &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.cnki.net/KCMS/detail/detail.aspx?dbcode=SCPD&amp;amp;dbname=SCPD202203&amp;amp;filename=CN114683882A&amp;amp;uniplatform=OVERSEA&amp;amp;v=Wl0I1qxkJ61qGbnSBuv3HE2BMOWsCJHi1ljgXATiiPKQ6z3JM4Q0odBUTKxNuRq4&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Available&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
