<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Ran Zhuoheng</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Ran Zhuoheng</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About Me</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/about-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/about-me/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am recently going to Hong Kong as a full-time research assistant and then registered as a full-time PhD student at &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.cityu.edu.hk/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;City University of Hong Kong&lt;/a&gt; which starting from 1 September. My postgraduate research has ended in 2022 at the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.ecs.soton.ac.uk/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;School of Electronics and Computer Science(ECS)&lt;/a&gt; of the University of Southampton, which is a leading academic institution and is ranked &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/education/ng-interactive/2021/sep/11/the-best-uk-universities-2022-rankings&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;1st in the UK for Electrical and Electronic Engineering&lt;/a&gt;. Before that, I graduated with a Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.) degree from &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://en.tiangong.edu.cn/main.htm&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Tiangong University&lt;/a&gt;, which is one of the universities in China under the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Double_First_Class_University_Plan&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&amp;ldquo;Double First Class Universities&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the world will need more IoT-based smart devices in the future, and they may be constrained by power consumption and size. Security will be the biggest issue for such devices under the background of the technology that has been fully developed. My current research interests include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AIoT security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital System Design with FPGA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wearable Medical Devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the general research programme, I am also currently working initially on the Excellence Research Programme which started from my research and preparation for my PhD at the University of Southampton. This project aimed to undertake an absolutely leading research over four years and publish it in a high-level journal, which might consist of several supportive top conferences. Scholars from around the world are welcome to contribute to this programme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more and contribute on &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/excellence-research/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Excellence Research Programme&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Excellence Research</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/excellence-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/excellence-research/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is generally challenging for most researchers to push human society one small step forward, even though we are usually assumed to be doing that in the eyes of non-researchers. Some of my previous work also looks like this, such as improving the work of other researchers in my field by a small step. This is quite normal because we can&amp;rsquo;t always contribute considerably during our short academic careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no so-called most excellent research in the world, which is a false proposition for anyone, whether for a beginner or a Nobel Prize winner in their field. But I always imagine that if I have one perfect research, I think it will be excellent and potentially provide enormous value to human society during my PhD academic career. It may seem not easy, but it is our primary responsibility in the eyes of non-researchers. At the same time, I think doing anything with a pure attitude is popular but challenging in any industry and field. Through this project, I expect to do at least one impressive piece of research that might be remarkable, which is the original motivation for setting up this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Hartley Library, University of Southampton, UK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5th September 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more and contribute on [Not available].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I am now actively seeking many views from scholars worldwide on a wide range of topics and will publish it at the appropriate time. You are welcome to contribute to this in any way possible, and all contributions and name will be permanently stored on my website when summarized.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Timeline</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/links/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/links/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ranzhuoheng.com/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
